Alright, now we want to look at the political environment.
Now, what we're talking about when we're talking about politics, or political environment, are they Democrat?
Are they Republican?
Are they, you know, in what extreme of what party are they?
Are they, you know, staunch Republicans?
Are they very, very liberal Democrats?
And, or are they anything?
Maybe they have no political party affiliation, they're not interested in politics, they could care less about politics.
Or maybe politics is their life.
What role does politics play in their life now in this moment, as well as how they were growing up.
Did they grow up in a very strict, staunch Republican household and so because of that now they're a very, very liberal Democrat?
Or vice a versa.
How does their political stance help determine who they are and how you are going to play them.